A Guide to the Richmond YWCA Archives 1893-1980
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series VI- Case Studies
  - Tyler, Gladys (Box-folder 53:45)
  - Tyler, Mamie (Box-folder 53:46)
  - Tyree, Chris and Harry (Box-folder 53:47)
  - Tyree, Edith (Box-folder 53:48)
  - Usherwood, Gertrude (Box-folder 53:49)
  - Usherwood, Hilda (Box-folder 53:50)
  - Vaughn, Betty (Box-folder 53:51)
  - Vaughn, Lemuel (Box-folder 53:52)
  - Vaughn, Margaret (Box-folder 53:53)
  - Via, Elizabeth (Box-folder 53:54)
  - Vick, Phyllis (Box-folder 53:55)
  - Vietch, Maude (Box-folder 53:56)
  - Vladka, Stella and LaRue (Box-folder 53:57)
  - Waddill, Gertrude (Box-folder 53:58)
  - Waddill, Lois (Box-folder 53:59)
  - Waldron, Christine (Box-folder 53:60)
  - Walker, Catherine (Box-folder 53:61)
  - Walker, Judith (Box-folder 53:62)
  - Waltson, Anne (Box-folder 53:63)
  - Walter, Dorothy (Box-folder 53:64)
  - Walthall, Audrey (Box-folder 53:65)
  - Walz, Judith (Box-folder 53:66)
  - Ward, Dorothy (Box-folder 53:67)
  - Warren, Evelyn (Box-folder 53:68)
  - Washington, Margaret (Box-folder 53:69)
  - Watkins, Emily (Box-folder 53:70)
  - Watson, Abbie (Box-folder 53:71)
  - Waxenbaum, Bessie (Box-folder 53:72)
  - Waymack, Kathryn (Box-folder 53:73)
  - Webb, June (Box-folder 53:74)
  - Webb, Nannie (Box-folder 53:75)
  - Webb, Nannie (Box-folder 53:76)
  - Webb, Vadie (Box-folder 53:77)
  - Weisenberger, Dorothy (Box-folder 53:78)
  - Weisman, Georgia (Box-folder 53:79)
  - Weiss, Nettie (Box-folder 53:80)
  - Wette, Ruth (Box-folder 53:81)
  - West, Edna (Box-folder 53:82)
  - West, Helen (Box-folder 53:83)
  - West, Sarah (Box-folder 53:84)
  - West, Virgie (Box-folder 53:85)
  - Western, Patricia (Box-folder 53:86)
  - Wheatley, Phyllis (Box-folder 53:87)
  - White, Evelyn (Box-folder 53:88)
  - White, Floyd (Box-folder 53:89)
  - White, Josephine (Box-folder 53:90)
  - Whitehead, Ola Belle (Box-folder 53:91)
  - Whiteside, Marian (Box-folder 53:92)
  - Whitlow, Jean (Box-folder 54:1)
  - Wilkers, Mrs. (Box-folder 54:2)
  - Wilkerson, Joan (Box-folder 54:3)
  - Wilkinson, Louise (Box-folder 54:4)
  - Wilcox, Mary (Box-folder 54:5)
  - Williams, Eugenia (Box-folder 54:6)
  - Williams, Evelyn (Box-folder 54:7)
  - Williams, Delores (Box-folder 54:8)
  - Williams, Louise (Box-folder 54:9)
  - Williams, Minnie (Box-folder 54:10)
  - Williams, Thelma (Box-folder 54:11)
  - Willingham, Elizabeth (Box-folder 54:12)
  - Willis, Angelia (Box-folder 54:13)
  - Willis, Louise (Box-folder 54:14)
  - Whiltshire, Mary (Box-folder 54:15)
  - Withers, Lucile (Box-folder 54:16)
  - Whittaker, Jean (Box-folder 54:17)
  - Womack, Estelle (Box-folder 54:18)
  - Wood, Ethel (Box-folder 54:19)
  - Wood, Sarah (Box-folder 54:20)
  - Woodcock, Doris (Box-folder 54:21)
  - Woods, Frances (Box-folder 54:22)
  - Woods, Jean (Box-folder 54:23)
  - Woodside, Nell (Box-folder 54:24)
  - Woody, Carrie (Box-folder 54:25)
  - Wormly, Elizabeth (Box-folder 54:26)
  - Worsham, Sadie (Box-folder 54:27)
  - Wright, Carolyn (Box-folder 54:28)
  - Wright, Irene (Box-folder 54:29)
  - Wright, Sue (Box-folder 54:30)
  - Wright, Virginia (Box-folder 54:31)
  - Yancey, Emma (Box-folder 54:32)
  - Young, Carolyn (Box-folder 54:33)
- Series VII--Committees and Programs
  - Activities and Programs given by the YWCA 1915, 1917, 1923, 1962, 1963 (Box-folder 55:1)
  - Advisory Committee undated (Box-folder 55:2)
  - Adult Activities undated (Box-folder 55:3-4)
  - Affirmative Action Committee 1980 (Box-folder 55:5-6)
  - After School Program 1977 (Box-folder 55:7)
  - Applications for Children's Countinuing Program undated (Box-folder 55:8)
  - Battered Women-Planning Committee 1977 (Box-folder 55:9)
  - Binford Girl Reserve Club-Lumsden Grant 1944 (Box-folder 55:10)
  - Black Women-Affiliate Program 1980 (Box-folder 55:11)
  - Camp Committee 1964 (Box-folder 55:12-14)
  - Casework Committee undated (Box-folder 56:1)
  - Christian Life undated (Box-folder 56:2)
  - Citizens Information Committee on Family Life and Sex Education 1967 (Box-folder 56:3)
  - City-Wide Young Adult Council 1952 (Box-folder 56:4)
  - Committee Job Descriptions undated (Box-folder 56:5)
  - Committee on Branch Relationship 1945 (Box-folder 56:6)
  - Committees and Board of Directors Lists 1930-1936 (Box-folder 56:7)
  - Committees 1949 (Box-folder 56:8)
  - Committees 1975 (Box-folder 56:9)
  - Committees 1977 (Box-folder 56:10)
  - Committees-Job Descriptions undated (Box-folder 56:11)
  - Committees-Building 1941-1949 (Box-folder 56:12)
  - Committees-Building 1962 (Box-folder 56:13)
  - Committees-Building 1956-1962 (Box-folder 56:14)
  - Committees--YWCA 1971 (Box-folder 56:15)
  - Community Council 1968 (Box-folder 22)
  - Community Relations Committee (Box-folder 22)
  - Dance Committee 1948 (Box-folder 23)
  - Decentralized Committee (Box-folder 23)
  - Earplay Project (Box-folder 23)
  - East End Girl Club Lumsdem Grant 1944 (Box-folder 23)
  - Education Council 1916-1920 (Box-folder 23)
  - Education Committee 1929-1931 (Box-folder 23)
  - Family and Children's Services (Box-folder 23)
  - Finance Committee 1960 (Box-folder 23)
  - Finance Committee-Budget Article for YWCA Magazine (Box-folder 23)
  - Finance Committee-Walford Study Committee 1953 (Box-folder 23)
  - Finance Committee-Walford Study Committee 1955 (Box-folder 23)
  - Food Service Committee (Box-folder 23)
  - Ford Foundation Project 1952 (Box-folder 23)
  - Gay Sombrero Club 1951-1952 (Box-folder 23)
  - Gay Sombrero Club 1953 (Box-folder 23)
  - Gay Sombrero Council (Box-folder 23)
  - Girl Scouts 1956 (Box-folder 23)
  - Girl Scouts 1957 (Box-folder 23)
  - Group Work Division Community Council 1952 (Box-folder 23)
  - Health Education Committee 1945-1947 (Box-folder 23)
  - Health Education Committee 1952-1958 (Box-folder 23)
  - Health Education-Swimming (Box-folder 23)
  - Health, Physical Education and Recreation (Box-folder 23)
  - Health, Physical Education and Recreation Committee 1970 (Box-folder 23)
  - House Committee 1937-1939 (Box-folder 23)
  - House Committee 1947-1952 (Box-folder 23)
  - HPER (Box-folder 23)
  - HPER Committee-Kaperette Camp (Box-folder 23)
  - HPER Committee-Summer Programs (Box-folder 23)
  - HPER-St. Catherine's Pool 1955-1956 (Box-folder 23)
  - Implementation Committee 1969 (Box-folder 24)
  - In-Service Training 1976 (Box-folder 24)
  - Inter Club Council-Purpose, Song, Hymn (Box-folder 24)
  - International Council 1970 (Box-folder 24)
  - Lesbian-Feminists (Box-folder 24)
  - Lift Club 1969 (Box-folder 24)
  - Maryland Volunteer Handbook (Box-folder 24)
  - Membership Committee 1923-1936 (Box-folder 24)
  - Membership Committee 1950 (Box-folder 24)
  - Membership Committee 1962 (Box-folder 24)
  - Membership Committee 1959-1965 (Box-folder 24)
  - Membership Committee 1971 (Box-folder 24)
  - Membership Committee Minutes (Box-folder 24)
  - Milady's Matinee Committee 1952 (Box-folder 24)
  - National B and P Council (Box-folder 24)
  - Nominating Committee 1946 (Box-folder 24)
  - Personnel 1937 (Box-folder 24)
  - Personnel Committee 1937-1939 (Box-folder 24)
  - Personnel Committee 1952 (Box-folder 24)
  - Personnel Committee-Staff 1945 (Box-folder 24)
  - Personnel Committee-Job Analysis 1941 (Box-folder 25)
  - Personnel Committee-Job Analysis 1942 (Box-folder 25)
  - Pioneer Club 1951-1953 (Box-folder 25)
  - Pioneer Club 1953 (Box-folder 25)
  - Pocahontas (Box-folder 25)
  - Pocahontas 1959 (Box-folder 25)
  - Police Affairs Committee 1960 (Box-folder 25)
  - Program Correlating Committee 1945-1946 (Box-folder 25)
  - Program Planning (Box-folder 25)
  - Public Affairs 1930 (Box-folder 25)
  - Public Affairs Committee 1970 (Box-folder 25)
  - Public Affairs Committee Activities 1948-1949 (Box-folder 25)
  - Public Affairs-Literature (Box-folder 25)
  - Public Relations Committee (Box-folder 25)
  - Public Relations Committee 1975 (Box-folder 26)
  - Religious Education Committee 1919-1923 (Box-folder 26)
  - Residence (Box-folder 26)
  - Richmond Area Community Council 1953 (Box-folder 26)
  - Richmond Community Action Program (Box-folder 26)
  - Richmond Teachers Association (Box-folder 26)
  - Social Service Committee (Box-folder 26)
  - Social Service Committee-Lumsden Fund (Box-folder 26)
  - Social Service Committee-Lumsden Fund Referrals (Box-folder 26)
  - Social Service Committee-Membership Fund Referrals (Box-folder 26)
  - Social Service Committee Minutes 1949-1952 (Box-folder 26)
  - Social Service Committee Minutes 1952 (Box-folder 26)
  - Social Service Committee Minutes 1950-1953 (Box-folder 26)
  - Social Service Committee Minutes 1953-1957 (Box-folder 26)
  - Social Service Committee Minutes 1960 (Box-folder 26)
  - Studies Committee (Box-folder 26)
  - Teen-Age Committee Minutes 1950 (Box-folder 26)
  - Teen Brides Club 1962 (Box-folder 26)
  - Teen Committee 1966 (Box-folder 26)
  - Teen Program 1966-1971 (Box-folder 26)
  - Tuesday Eve Program 1953 (Box-folder 26)
  - Union Seminary (Box-folder 26)
  - Various YWCA Programs (Box-folder 26)
  - Virginia Assembly 1948 (Box-folder 27)
  - Virginia Assembly 1950 (Box-folder 27)
  - Virginia Child Labor Committee 1947 (Box-folder 26)
  - Volunteer Leadership Committee (Box-folder 27)
  - Volunteers 1952 (Box-folder 27)
  - William Fox Sub-Teen Club 1968 (Box-folder 27)
  - Wider Opportunities for Women-Richmond (Box-folder 27)
  - WIN Orientation Program (Box-folder 27)
  - Winter Classes at YWCA 1970 (Box-folder 27)
  - Workshops (Box-folder 27)
  - World Fellowship Committee and World Mutual Service Committee (Box-folder 27)
  - World Mutual Service Committee (Box-folder 27)
  - Young Adult Committee 1949-1950 (Box-folder 27)
  - Young Adult Committee 1950 (Box-folder 27)
  - Young Adult Committee 1952 (Box-folder 27)
  - Young Adult Committee 1953 (Box-folder 27)
  - Young Adult Council 1951 (Box-folder 27)
  - Young Women's Association-Report on Examination 1955-1956 (Box-folder 27)
  - Youth Committee/Youth Program (Box-folder 27)
  - Y-Teen Committee (Box-folder 27)
  - YWCA Advisory Committee 1952-1957 (Box-folder 27)
- General Files
  - AARP 1970 (Box-folder 28)
  - Ability Grouping-Tracking (Connecticut Study) 1976 (Box-folder 28)
  - ACLU-Oral History (Box-folder 28)
  - ACLU Proposal (Box-folder 28)
  - ACLU Women's Rights Mailing List (Box-folder 28)
  - A Commemorative Conference on Feminist Theory 1979 (Box-folder 28)
  - Adult Dialogue-Group III 1968 (Box-folder 28)
  - Affiliate Directors Influence (Box-folder 28)
  - Aging (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Board Minutes 1950-1951 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Dinner 1970 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Meetings of Whole Association 1945 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Report 1946 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Report-Business and Professional Department 1945 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Report-Industrial Department 1941-1945 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Report-Narrative 1952 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Report-Statistics 1952 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Report to YWCA Board-Lumsden Fund 1960 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Report to YWCA Board President 1951-1955 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Reports 1937 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Reports 1937-1940 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Reports 1941 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Reports 1942 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Reports 1943 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Reports 1944 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Reports 1942-1946 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Reports 1946 (Box-folder 28)
  - Annual Reports 1963 (Box-folder 28)
  - Applicants for Lumsden (Box-folder 28)
  - Application for Lumsden Grants (Box-folder 28)
  - Application Form Information (Box-folder 28)
  - Appraisal of YWCA Properties 1959 (Box-folder 28)
  - Area Council Meeting 1952 (Box-folder 28)
  - Association Review (Box-folder 28)
  - Association Review Reports 1972 (Box-folder 28)
  - Attendance Records 1953 (Box-folder 28)
  - Audio-Visual Equipment 1969 (Box-folder 28)
  - Authorization to Mrs. Jones (Box-folder 28)
  - Automobile 1938 (Box-folder 28)
  - Barrett Industrial Y-Teen Membership Fees (Box-folder 28)
  - Battered Women Conference Evaluation Form (Box-folder 28)
  - Battered WOmen Information-Miscellaneous 1977 (Box-folder 28)
  - Battered Women Memorandum 1980 (Box-folder 28)
  - Board Meeting Information 1943 (Box-folder 28)
  - Board Minutes 1961 (Box-folder 28)
  - Richmond YWCA Archives (Box-folder 28)
  - Bridge 1953 (Box-folder 28)
  - Brochure Estimates (Box-folder 28)
  - Brochure Material (Box-folder 28)
  - Bryan Park-Shangri La (Box-folder 28)
  - Cafeteria Management 1953 (Box-folder 29)
  - Ceraminc File-Miss Croak 1951-1953 (Box-folder 29)
  - Charge Accounts-YWCA 1970 (Box-folder 29)
  - China Painting and Oil Designs 1852-1953 (Box-folder 29)
  - Christmas Candlelighting Ceremonial 1961 (Box-folder 29)
  - Christmas Decorations 1953 (Box-folder 29)
  - Christmas Prelude 1941 (Box-folder 29)
  - Civil Rights-National Program 1948 (Box-folder 29)
  - Commercial Lighting Products 1971 (Box-folder 29)
  - Committee Minutes 1961 (Box-folder 29)
  - Community Council Study 1953 (Box-folder 29)
  - Community-Richmond 1947 (Box-folder 29)
  - Computer/Mailing Service (Box-folder 29)
  - Conference Evaluation 1978 (Box-folder 29)
  - Conference Logs 1977 (Box-folder 29)
  - Conference on Battered Women 1978 (Box-folder 29)
  - Conference Registration 1978 (Box-folder 29)
  - Conferences 1970 (Box-folder 29)
  - Conferences-Claytor 1967 (Box-folder 29)
  - Conference Sites (Box-folder 29)
  - Conference-Virginia 1966-1967 (Box-folder 29)
  - Consumer Forum 1980 (Box-folder 29)
  - Convention 1973 (Box-folder 29)
  - Convention at Home 1945 (Box-folder 29)
  - Cooking 1951-1952 (Box-folder 29)
  - Correspondence 1953 (Box-folder 29)
  - Correspondence 1975-1976 (Box-folder 29)
  - Correspondence 1978-1979 (Box-folder 29)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2) (Box-folder 29)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2) 1979 (Box-folder 29)
  - Correspondence 1980 (Box-folder 29)
  - Correspondence from Lucile Cook (Box-folder 29)
  - Crafts 1951-1952 (Box-folder 29)
  - Desk Registry (Box-folder 30)
  - Designs for Christmas 1952 (Box-folder 30)
  - Directory of Personnel-Local Departments of Public Welfare 1952 (Box-folder 30)
  - Directory of Personnel-Virginia Department of Welfare and institutions 1951 (Box-folder 30)
  - Drugs (Box-folder 30)
  - Duties of Social Service Committee 1954 (Box-folder 30)
  - Educational Materials (Box-folder 30)
  - Education: Title IX-Compliance Guidelines 1976 (Box-folder 30)
  - Education: Title IX-Reports, Articles 1976 (Box-folder 30)
  - Euthenics Committee 1941 (Box-folder 30)
  - Family Life 1945-1949 (Box-folder 30)
  - Fieldwork Students from Assembly's Training School 1952-1953 (Box-folder 30)
  - Final Copy Graphics and Layout (Box-folder 31)
  - Flower Arranging 1950 (Box-folder 30)
  - Flyers (Box-folder 30)
  - Flyers-Teenage Department 1961 (Box-folder 30)
  - Food for Thought (Box-folder 30)
  - Food Service Committee Minutes 1947-1957 (Box-folder 30)
  - Food Service Equipment-Supplies 1969 (Box-folder 30)
  - Foundation (Box-folder 30)
  - Furniture Refinishing 1952-1953 (Box-folder 30)
  - Gay Sombrero Minutes 1950-1953 (Box-folder 30)
  - Grant Application-American Civil Liberties Union of Virginia 1977 (Box-folder 30)
  - Grants-National Tracking, Suspensions Testing 1976 (Box-folder 30)
  - Gun Control Stand (Box-folder 30)
  - Hannah Harrison School (Box-folder 30)
  - Hate Mail (Box-folder 30)
  - Health Certificates (Box-folder 30)
  - Health Education 1948 (Box-folder 30)
  - Household Furnishings 1968 (Box-folder 30)
  - Information on Case Work Agencies in Richmond 1954 (Box-folder 30)
  - Information on Dr. Lumsden (Box-folder 30)
  - Inner-Office Correspondence (Box-folder 30)
  - Inner Security Questionaire (Box-folder 30)
  - Insurance 1970 (Box-folder 30)
  - Interior Decorating (Box-folder 30)
  - Inventory of Public Relations Material (Box-folder 30)
  - Invitation to Virginia Child Labor Conference 1947 (Box-folder 30)
  - Job Description Notes (Box-folder 30)
  - Job Evaluation Form 1949 (Box-folder 30)
  - J.P. Stevens Campaign 1980-1981 (Box-folder 30)
  - Juvenile Delinquency Project 1970 (Box-folder 30)
  - Juvenile Detention Home Project-Transportation 1947 (Box-folder 30)
  - Legal Aspects of Lumsden-Eliz Tompkins, Attorney (Box-folder 30)
  - Legal Requests 198 (Box-folder 30)
  - Legislation 1969 (Box-folder 30)
  - Leisure Time Activities-Questionaire 1952 (Box-folder 30)
  - Lists and Advertising on Cleaning Supply Companies 1943 (Box-folder 30)
  - Literature Display 1978 (Box-folder 30)
  - Lumsden Fund 1948-1950 (Box-folder 30)
  - Lumsden Fund 1951 (Box-folder 30)
  - Lumsden Fund-Record Regarding Policy 1933 (Box-folder 30)
  - Lumsden Fund Report 1943 (Box-folder 30)
  - Lumsden Fund-Reports (Box-folder 30)
  - Lumsden Minutes 1949 (Box-folder 30)
  - Lumsden Report 1957-1959 (Box-folder 30)
  - Madison Project-Lumsden Grant (Box-folder 31)
  - Maintenance-Cleaning 1969 (Box-folder 31)
  - Maintenance Employee's Standards 1945 (Box-folder 31)
  - Marriage Course 1950-1951 (Box-folder 31)
  - Mechanical Equipment-Building 1963 (Box-folder 31)
  - Media Order Forms (Box-folder 31)
  - Media/PSA's 1978 (Box-folder 31)
  - Membership Enrollment 1943 (Box-folder 31)
  - Membership YWCA 1948 (Box-folder 31)
  - Memorandum Concerning Master File 1943 (Box-folder 31)
  - Mental Hygiene Material (Box-folder 31)
  - Metal Crafts (Box-folder 31)
  - Midwest Academy (Box-folder 31)
  - Milady's Matinee 1953 (Box-folder 31)
  - Milady's Matinee-Chariman 1951-1952 (Box-folder 31)
  - Milady's Matinee-Nursery 1952-1953 (Box-folder 31)
  - Milady's Matinee-Publicity 1952 (Box-folder 31)
  - Milady's Matinee-Teachers (Box-folder 31)
  - Milady's Matinee-Questionaire 1953 (Box-folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Minutes 1943-1948 (Box-folder 31)
  - Model City (Box-folder 31)
  - Monthly Reports 1951 (Box-folder 31)
  - Monthly Reports-Statistics 1952 (Box-folder 31)
  - MS Foundation (Box-folder 31)
  - Narrative Report (Monthly) 1952 (Box-folder 31)
  - Narratives-Teen 1961-1964 (Box-folder 31)
  - National Bulletins (Box-folder 31)
  - National Narrative Report 1952-1953 (Box-folder 31)
  - National Staff Correspondence 1951-1952 (Box-folder 31)
  - National Y-Teen Confernce 1965 (Box-folder 31)
  - National YWCA Day 1947 (Box-folder 31)
  - Nationwide Business and Professional Girls' Banquet (Box-folder 31)
  - Narrative Reports-Monthly 1953 (Box-folder 31)
  - Neighborhood Projects 1940 (Box-folder 31)
  - Newsletter Additions (Box-folder 31)
  - Newspaper Ad (Box-folder 31)
  - Office Furnishings-Equipment/Supplies 1969 (Box-folder 31)
  - Out of Town Inquiries (Box-folder 31)
  - Payment Request Forms (Box-folder 31)
  - Personnel Information 1951 (Box-folder 31)
  - Personnel Policies 1948 (Box-folder 31)
  - Personnel Policy Regarding Case Workers 1955 (Box-folder 31)
  - Photography (Box-folder 31)
  - Phyllis Wheatley 1941 (Box-folder 31)
  - Police Reserve Proposal (Box-folder 31)
  - Practical Politics (Box-folder 31)
  - Printers 1970 (Box-folder 31)
  - Program Equipment 1969 (Box-folder 31)
  - Program Ideas (Box-folder 31)
  - Program Participants 1950 (Box-folder 31)
  - Program Plan-YWCA 1970-1975 (Box-folder 31)
  - Program Staff Meetings, etc. 1953 (Box-folder 31)
  - Public Affairs Minutes (Box-folder 32)
  - Public Assistance-Memo, Bills, Letters 1977 (Box-folder 32)
  - Publications (Box-folder 32)
  - Publicity (Box-folder 32)
  - Publicity 1951 (Box-folder 32)
  - Publicity 1952 (Box-folder 32)
  - Publicity 1953 (Box-folder 32)
  - Publicity 1971 (Box-folder 32)
  - Publicity Newspaper 1952 (Box-folder 32)
  - Publicity Releases 1971 (Box-folder 32)
  - Publicity (Young Adult Department) 1949-1950 (Box-folder 32)
  - Public Relations Bulletin Board and Show Case (Box-folder 32)
  - Public Affairs (Box-folder 32)
  - Public Relations Channels 1961-1966 (Box-folder 32)
  - Public Relations Information (Box-folder 32)
  - Public Relations Job Description (Box-folder 32)
  - Public Relations Mailing List (Box-folder 32)
  - Public Relations Minutes 1964-1971 (Box-folder 32)
  - Public Relations Minutes 1967-1968 (Box-folder 32)
  - Public Relations Releases 1970 (Box-folder 32)
  - Public Relations Survey (Box-folder 32)
  - Radio and TV Scripts (Box-folder 32)
  - Receipts-Social Services Department (Box-folder 32)
  - Registration for Class Forms (Box-folder 32)
  - Registration Procedures 1952-1953 (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on ACLU (Box-folder 32)
  - Rerport on AL, AK, AR, AZ (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on Ca, Co, CT (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on DC (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on DE, GA, FL (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on HI, IL, IN, KS (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on KY, LA, MA (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on MS, MT, NE (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on MD, ME, MI, MN, MO (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on NC (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on ND, NH, NJ, NM, NV (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on NY (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on OH, OK, OR (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on PA, PR, RI, SC (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on SA, TN, TX (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on UT, Va, VT (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on WA, WI, WV, WY (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on Battered Women 1978 (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on Donations (Box-folder 32)
  - Report on Graphics (Box-folder 32)
  - Reports to be Added (Box-folder 32)
  - Resources (Box-folder 33)
  - Requests for Publicity (Box-folder 33)
  - Requisitions (Box-folder 33)
  - Revenue Sharing 1980 (Box-folder 33)
  - ROAR Health Certificates (Box-folder 33)
  - Sample Committee Folder 1952 (Box-folder 33)
  - Scholarship Applications 1954 (Box-folder 33)
  - Scholarship Resources Available in Richmond 1955 (Box-folder 33)
  - Scholarships 1955 (Box-folder 33)
  - Second Baptist Children 1939 (Box-folder 33)
  - Seminars (Box-folder 33)
  - Setting Up Conference-Roslyn 1952 (Box-folder 33)
  - Sewing 1953 (Box-folder 33)
  - Sewing Class (Box-folder 33)
  - Sex Education 1969 (Box-folder 33)
  - Shangri-La (Box-folder 33)
  - Shop Talk and YWCA Magazine 1952 (Box-folder 33)
  - Social Service Project Report 1948-1951 (Box-folder 33)
  - Social Security (Box-folder 33)
  - Southern Changes-Health Care in the South (Box-folder 33)
  - Southern Changes-Issues of Magazine 1980 (Box-folder 33)
  - Southern Region YWCA News 1973 (Box-folder 33)
  - Southern State Coordinates (Box-folder 33)
  - Speakers/Panelists 1978 (Box-folder 33)
  - Spot Announcements (Box-folder 33)
  - Square Dance and Receipts (Box-folder 33)
  - Staff Calendars (Box-folder 33)
  - Staff Manual 1952 (Box-folder 33)
  - Staff Meeting-Minutes and Handouts (Box-folder 33)
  - Staff Minutes 1952 (Box-folder 33)
  - Statistical Report Form (Box-folder 33)
  - Statistical Resort Group Form (Box-folder 33)
  - Statistical Reports 1953 (Box-folder 33)
  - Statistical Report Sheets and Information (Box-folder 33)
  - Statistical Report-Volunteers (Box-folder 33)
  - Statistical Story of Richmond YWCA 1953 (Box-folder 33)
  - Steinmetz Conference 1977 (Box-folder 33)
  - Subscriptions 1953 (Box-folder 33)
  - Survey-Leisure Time 1952 (Box-folder 33)
  - Summer Conference 1953 (Box-folder 33)
  - Summer School Abroad 1963 (Box-folder 33)
  - Teachers and Classes-Idea Folder (Box-folder 33)
  - Teen Narratives 1967 (Box-folder 33)
  - Thanksgiving (Box-folder 33)
  - The Political Prognosis for the 97th Congress 1980 (Box-folder 33)
  - The YWCA Magazine 1971 (Box-folder 33)
  - The IX-Grievance Procedures 1976 (Box-folder 33)
  - Tray Painiting 1952-1953 (Box-folder 33)
  - Treasurer's Statement 1947 (Box-folder 33)
  - Trust Officers' Information (Box-folder 33)
  - Twenty-Fourth National Convention 1967 (Box-folder 33)
  - Various Committee Minutes (Box-folder 33)
  - VCU (Box-folder 33)
  - VCU Facilities 1978 (Box-folder 33)
  - Vehicles 1969 (Box-folder 33)
  - Virginia/Carolina Y-Teen Conference 1963 (Box-folder 33)